随便哪天
On any given day,
我们学校的体育馆都会发生各式各样的恐怖事
our school gymnasium presented a cocktail of horrors.
从日常丢脸
From daily humiliation...
到学校认可的暴力
...to school-sanctioned violence...
但每年有那么一天  体育馆会摇身一变
But one day a year, the gymnasium was transformed
成为学习的殿堂
into a haven of learning
这都要感谢一个了不起的惯例
thanks to a remarkable institution
科学展
known as the science fair.
全体学生都有机会
A chance for the student body to come together
哪种饮料让我打嗝最响
以研究和进步之名齐聚一堂
in the name of research and progress.
有些人毫不努力
Uh, while some did the bare minimum...
声级计
其他人则喜欢作秀多过原始数据
...and others preferred razzamatazz over raw data,
范德格拉夫起电机
产生静电高压的装置
我致力于拯救人类不被致命小行星灭绝
I set out to save humanity from deadly asteroids.
小行星的追踪和偏移
由谢尔顿·李·库珀呈现
我把内容都整齐排在三块硬纸板上
And made it all neatly fit on three poster boards.
科学展也许是场比赛
The science fair may be a competition,
但当目的是分享知识时  我们都是赢家
but when the goal is promoting knowledge, we're all winners.
赢得
And the winner
梅德福高中科学展的就是...
of the Medford High School Science Fair is...
苏安·拉德洛
SueAnn Ludlow!
你逗我呢吧
You've got to be kidding me!
谢利
Shelly.
你们这些人都疯了
You people are crazy!
好了
Hey. ‭All right.
你们在赞美平庸
You're celebrating mediocrity!
平庸
Mediocrity!
平庸啊
♪ 世上没人比我强壮 ♪
♪ Nobody else is stronger than I am ♪
♪ 昨天我移了一座山 ♪
♪ Yesterday I moved a mountain ♪
♪ 我相信我能当你的英雄 ♪
♪ I bet I could be your hero ♪
♪ 我是个了不起的小家伙 ♪
♪ I am a mighty little man ♪
少
年
谢尔顿
我回房间去了
I'll be in my room.
别这样  谢利
Oh, come on, Shelly.
你还是得到优等奖了呀
You still got an honorable mention.
别提起我的伤心事了
Stop reminding me.
我讨厌看到他如此不开心
I hate to see him so upset.
给他点时间嘛  他会冷静下来的
Well, give him a little time, he'll calm down.
狗屁不通
Fiddle-faddle!
都骂脏字了
The F word.
他真的很生气
He's real mad.
生活中并非次次能赢  他需要学会这点
You don't always win in life, he needs to learn that.
我知道  但这对小男孩来说是很激烈的情绪
I know, but these are big feelings for a little boy.
每个人都有这种情绪
They're feelings everybody has.
这是成长必经阶段
It's part of growing up.
说得也是
I guess.
狗狗屎
Poodle poop!
好了
Okay.
得有人去教这孩子如何骂脏话了
Somebody's got to teach this kid to swear,
这样很丢人
it's embarrassing.
优等奖
谢尔顿  听着
Sheldon, listen,
我知道输很难接受
I know losing ain't easy.
我在橄榄球场上经常要面对这个
I deal with it on the football field all the time.
就像我们去年对纳卡多奇斯队那场重要的比赛
It's like that big game we had last year against Nacogdoches.
中场休息时我们落后28分
We were down 28 points at the half.
当时在下雨  一片泥泞
It was raining, it was muddy.
看台上的人全都回家了
Everybody in the stands had gone home.
但不知怎的  我们成功在终场前一分钟
But somehow, we managed to claw our way back
追成平手
to a tie with a minute left.
然后他们传了一个孤注一掷的长传
And then, they threw a Hail Mary,
接球员出界了
and the receiver stepped out of bounds,
但裁判没看到
but the ref didn't see it.
经历了这么多后  我们输在了错判上
After all that, we lose on a bad call.
相信我  我当时气炸了
Believe me, I was furious.
但我忍住了
But I sucked it up,
我走到球场另一边  跟他们握手
and I walked across that field and I shook their hands.
你刚说的我一个字都没听进去
I didn't hear a word you said.
好吧
Okay.
动物细胞  植物细胞
动物细胞有细胞膜
So while an animal cell has a membrane,
植物细胞则有细胞膜和细胞壁
a plant cell has a membrane and a cell wall.
谁在乎啊
Who cares?
谢尔顿  你在干什么
Sheldon, what are you doing?
目无尊长  老师
Being disrespectful, sir.
为什么
Ah. How come?
因为我对学校制度幻灭了
Because I'm disillusioned with the school system.
小乔治  你知道他怎么回事吗
Georgie, do you know what's going on with him?
事实上  我在努力无视他
Actually, I'm trying to ignore it.
你把脚放下来
Well, get your feet off the desk.
如果我不放呢
What if I don't?
老师叫我来见彼得森校长
I was sent to see Principal Petersen.
这次你又做了什么
What is it this time?
青春期叛逆
Youthful rebellion.
我还没变声  但我的态度变了
My voice hasn't changed yet, but my attitude has.
我通知他你来了
I'll let him know you're here.
麻利点儿
You do that.
女士
Ma'am.
谢尔顿·库珀在外面
Sheldon Cooper's outside.
这次是谁叫他来的
Who sent him now?
-吉文斯  -你知道吗
- Givens. ‭- Well, you know what?
吉文斯应该爷们一点
Givens needs to man up.
库珀只是个小男孩
Cooper's a little boy.
对付他一点都不难啊
It's not hard to handle him.
我叫他进来
I'll send him in.
先等一下
H-Hold on a minute, just...
他知道我在办公室吗
Does he know I'm in here?
全体学生和教员请注意
Attention, students and faculty.
糟了
Oh, no.
我是谢尔顿·李·库珀
This is Sheldon Lee Cooper.
什么鬼
What the hell?
我们被教导努力会有回报  但那不是真的
We're taught that hard work pays off, but that's not true.
我想出了从致命小行星手中
I came up with a solution to save Earth
拯救地球的方法
from killer asteroids,
却在科学展中
and lost the science fair
输给了苏安·拉德洛  及她的炸头毛机器
to SueAnn Ludlow, and her frizzy hair machine.
但输的不只是我  我们都输了
But it wasn't just me who lost, we all lost.
你们清醒一点
Wake up, people.
这个体制已经崩坏了
The system's broken.
真正的创新不被重视
Real innovation isn't valued.
这年头  浮夸和有型才是王道
Nowadays, it's all about flash and style.
都怪MTV台
I blame MTV.
音乐电视网频道  节目主要面向青少年
有时被人诟病推广脑残内容
幸好我的父母订不起有线电视台
Luckily, my parents can't afford cable.
我们订得起啦
We can afford it.
我敦促你们都起来反抗
I urge you all to rise up.
法不责众  不可能全都去见校长
They can't send everyone to the principal's office.
在课上嚼口香糖  改用一号铅笔
Chew gum in class, use a number one pencil,
疯起来吧
go nuts.
谢尔顿·李·库珀发言完毕
This is Sheldon Lee Cooper signing off.
生生不息  繁荣昌盛
Live long and prosper.
有种你别跑  小兔崽子
You better run, you little punk!
真不敢相信你让他饿着肚子就上床睡觉
I can't believe you sent him to bed without his dinner.
没错
That's right.
而且今晚还是吃热狗意粉
On spaghetti and hot dog night.
-够残忍  -他必须学会教训
- That's rough. ‭- He's got to learn.
我们聊点别的吧
Let's talk about something else.
小乔治  你今天过得怎么样
Georgie, how was your day?
我弟弟告诉全校的人我们家订不起有线电视
My brother told the entire school we can't afford cable.
对哦
Oh, right.
米希
Missy?
本来挺好  直到听说我们订不起有线电视
Good, until I learned we can't afford cable.
我一直在思考  我有话想说
I've been thinking, and there's something I'd like to say.
除非是道歉  否则就不用说了
Unless it's an apology, I don't want to hear it.
我要放弃科学
I'm quitting science.
并不是道歉
Not an apology.
打他屁股  爸爸
Spank him, Dad.
我真的开始担心谢利了
I'm really getting worried about Shelly.
之前是发脾气  现在还要放弃科学
Acting out, and now quitting science?
他一定马上就重新沉迷科学的
Oh, I'm sure he'll get right back to it.
我也戒过烟和赌博很多次了
I've quit smoking and gambling plenty of times.
打开我包包看看
Hmm. Look in my purse.
里面只有烟和刮刮乐彩票
Nothing but cigarettes and scratchers.
也许他该找人谈谈
Maybe he should talk to somebody.
做梦
Not it.
我是指跟专业人士谈  乔治
I meant a professional, George.
不过你可真是"好"爸爸啊
But way to be a dad.
医学中心
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
谢谢你这么快就腾出时间见我们  医生
Thank you for seeing us on such short notice, Doctor.
不客气
Oh, not a problem.
谢尔顿
Sheldon,
我记得你
I remember you.
你记得我吗
Do you remember me?
我什么都记得
I remember everything.
好吧
Okay.
二位女士请随意
Uh, you two, make yourselves comfortable.
我跟我兄弟谢尔顿
Me and my main man Sheldon are gonna go
要到我办公室里好好聊聊
have a little chitchat in my office.
我不喜欢聊天  我也不是你兄弟
I don't like chitchat, and I'm not your main man.
好极了
Right on.
玩得开心
Have fun.
谢尔顿  我知道你改变主意
Now, Sheldon, I understand you've changed your mind
不想当科学家了
about being a scientist.
你打算说我不能这么做吗
And you're gonna say I can't?
不  我觉得那样很棒
No. I think that's great.
-真的吗  -嗯
- You do? - ‭Yeah.
我认为对人生选择保持开放态度是好事
I think it's important to keep your options open.
让我告诉你一个小故事
Let me tell you a little story
主角是一个非常聪明的小男孩
about an extremely smart young boy.
我吗
Me?
是我
Me.
有很长一段时间
For the longest time,
我都以为自己会成为
I thought I was gonna be
一名专业花样滑冰运动员
a professional figure skater.
然后你跟我一样对那个领域幻想破灭了吗
And then you became disenchanted with the field like I did?
正是
Exactly.
有人穿着冰鞋在我脚上滑过
Someone skated right over my foot.
从此没戏了
And that was that.
我不确定这是一回事
I'm not sure that's the same thing.
你失去激情与我失去脚趾的方式如出一辙
I'd say you lost your passion the way I lost my big toe.
别在上面乱画
Don't draw in that.
我们结束了
Hey. We're all done.
-怎么样  -很好
- How'd it go? ‭- Great.
我感觉好多了
I feel a lot better.
实在太棒了
Well, that's just wonderful.
那你要继续研究科学吗
So, you're going back to science?
不  事实上我要离科学越远越好
No. In fact, I'm going as far away from science as possible.
我打算投身艺术行业
I plan to pursue the arts.
哪种艺术
What kind of arts?
我决定以后要当演员
I've decided to become an actor.
不出所料
Of course you have.
他为什么想学演戏
Why's he want to study acting?
医生鼓励他尝试不一样的东西
The doctor encouraged him to try something different.
也许他能学会表现得像正常人
Maybe he'll learn to act normal.
不如你学学如何友善待人吧
How about you learn to act nice?
你们都不懂欣赏我的幽默感
You people don't appreciate my sense of humor.
只要他开始在学校乖乖的
As long as he starts behaving himself in school,
我不在乎他做什么
I don't care what he does.
其实我20几岁时  曾在一个社区小剧团
You know, I actually did a little community theater
演过戏
back in my 20s.
是吗
Is that so?
我在《俄克拉荷马》演了个很棒的角色
I had a good part in Oklahoma.
♪ 我就是一个无法拒绝的女孩 ♪
♪ I'm just a girl who can't say no. ♪
拒绝什么
Say no to what?
这个嘛
Well...
无法拒绝吃蔬菜
To, uh, eating her vegetables.
特别好玩
It was fun.
不过我很肯定排戏
But I'm pretty sure doing plays
只是为了能在后台一起换衣服
is just an excuse to change in front of each other backstage.
-真的吗  -是啊
- Really? ‭- Yeah.
戏剧圈的人可爱脱衣服了
Theater folk just love to take their clothes off.
有多少人看过你的裸体
How many people saw you naked?
很多
A lot.
-妈妈  -够了
- Mom. - ‭Enough.
你们也不懂我的幽默
Y'all don't understand my sense of humor, either.
你好  请问你是伦迪老师[先生]吗
Hello. Are you Mr. Lundy?
我父亲才是伦迪先生
My father is Mr. Lundy.
那我应该怎么称呼你
Well, then what should I call you?
伦迪先生吧
I guess Mr. Lundy.
毕竟我爸不在了
My father's dead.
他们告诉我你是戏剧部的负责人
I was told you're the head of the drama department.
没错  也是女子排球队的教练
Mm-hmm, and the girls' volleyball coach,
偷偷告诉你  那边的人戏才多
which, between us, is the real drama department.
这是个笑话吗
Was that a joke?
我觉得是
I thought so.
你有什么事
Can I help you?
我想当演员
I'm interested in becoming an actor.
那敢情好
Well, good for you.
你来这里就对了
You've come to the right place.
我也是个职业演员呢
You know, I-I've been a professional actor
当了好多好多年了
for years and years.
真的吗  你演过什么
Really? What have you been in?
你看过一个床垫的广告吗
Well, have you seen the mattress madness commercials
在68频道播出的
on channel 68?
我又柔软又结实
I'm soft and firm
该软则软  该结实则结实
in all the right places.
你是名人啊
Wow. You're famous.
这个嘛...
Well, I...
我也曾经出演过
And I was Carbucketty
达拉斯沃斯堡市制作的音乐剧《猫》
in the Dallas-Fort Worth Players production of Cats.
看到没
Did you see that?
不要  我怕猫
No, I'm afraid of cats.
你知道那些猫都是演员演的吧
Well, you realize the cats are just the actors.
我还是不想冒这个险
I still wouldn't risk it.
你真是个奇特的孩子  但你应该能行
You're an odd boy, but you make it work.
好了  试镜是在下周
Anyway, uh, auditions are next week.
-到时候欢迎你来  -太好了
- You're welcome to come on by. - Excellent.
我借了一本讲演戏的书
I checked out a book on acting
到时候我应该已经掌握得差不多了
so I should have the hang of it by then.
我喜欢你这自信
Well, I like that confidence.
谢谢  大多数人都觉得反感
Thank you. Most people find it off-putting.
我也能理解
I can see that.
要想掌握演戏  我先让自己
To master acting, I immersed myself
沉浸在各种不同类型的作品里  从默片
in all forms of the genre, from silent films
1927年的杰出默片《将军号》
到现代经典
to modern classics...
1963年由希区柯克执导的经典电影《鸟》
到反逻辑的实验性作品
...to logic-defying experimental work.
1952年的不朽音乐歌舞片杰作《雨中曲》
歌曲名《Good morning》
♪ 睡懒觉最棒了 ♪
♪ It's great to stay up late... ♪
他们为什么都在唱歌
Why are they all singing?
因为这是歌舞片啊
Because it's a musical.
他们为什么不能用说的呢
But why can't they just say it?
那就不够"歌舞"了  不是吗
Well, that wouldn't be very musical, would it?
♪ 繁星在闪耀 ♪
♪ The stars were shining bright... ♪
而且他们的音乐是从哪来的啊
And where is the music coming from?
你太较真了
You're thinking about it too much.
♪ 所以  早安 ♪
♪ So, good morning ♪
♪ 早安 ♪
♪ Good morning... ♪
而且他们为什么都会跳同一套舞啊
And how do they all know the same dance?
-别问了  -小饼饼
- Come on. - ‭Moonpie.
《演员的自我修养》
你在找什么
What are you looking for?
胸针
A brooch.
什么是胸针
What's a brooch?
是一种首饰
It's a piece of jewelry.
在演戏的书里有个小练习
In my acting book, there's an exercise
就是你得用令人信服的方式寻找一个胸针
where you look for a missing brooch in a convincing way.
为什么
Why?
根据书中的背景故事  这个是我朋友送的
According to the story, it was given to me by a friend
让我变卖好继续读戏剧学校  被我弄丢了
so I could afford to stay in drama school, but now it's gone.
祝你早日找到啦
Well, good luck finding it.
谢谢
Thanks.
等等
Wait.
你真的相信了我是在找东西
You really believed I was looking for something.
我成功啦
I did it.
我是个演员
I'm an actor.
你是个神经病
You're a freak.
这胸针到底是跑哪去了
Oh, where the heck is that brooch?
如果我能改变
If I can change,
你也能改变
and you can change,
那每个人都能改变
everybody can change.
谢谢你  伊娃
Thank you, Eva.
谢谢你朗读拳击片《洛奇4》台词的演出
That was a-a lovely reading from Rocky IV.
好了  库珀先生
All right, Mr. Cooper.
舞台是你的了
The stage is yours.
谢谢
Thank you.
我想要先来一段《李尔王》中的独白
I'd like to begin with a monologue from King Lear.
怎么
What?
演员开演前  你应该说"祝开演成功"[断条腿]
I believe you're supposed to say "break a leg."
抱歉
Sorry.
祝开演成功
Break a leg.
可怜的衣不蔽体的穷人们
Poor naked wretches,
不管你们身处何方
whereso'er you are,
都要忍受这样无情的暴风雨的袭击
that bide the pelting of this pitiless storm.
你们头无片瓦  饥肠辘辘
How shall your houseless heads and unfed sides,
穿着百孔千疮的衣服  如何抵挡
your looped and windowed raggedness defend you
这样的天气
from seasons such as these?
哦  我对这样的事关心得太少了
Oh, I've ta'en too little care of this.
吞下这剂药吧  衣着华丽的贵人
Take physic, pomp.
让你体验一下穷人的痛苦
Expose thyself to feel what wretches feel,
好把多余的财物分给他们
that thou may shake the superflux to them
使上天显得更加公平
and show the heavens more just.
我了个天啊
Holy mackerel.
♪ 阿根廷  别为我哭泣 ♪
♪ Don't cry for me, Argentina ♪
音乐剧《艾薇塔》与歌舞电影《贝隆夫人》中的名曲
《阿根廷别为我哭泣》
♪ 事实上我从未离开过你 ♪
♪ The truth is I never left you ♪
♪ 在那段狂野岁月里 ♪
♪ All through my wild days ♪
♪ 疯狂历程中 ♪
♪ My mad existence ♪
♪ 我都谨记诺言 ♪
♪ I kept my promise ♪
♪ 别将我拒之门外 ♪
♪ Don't keep your distance... ♪
♪ 我有雏菊 ♪
♪ I've got daisies ♪
1951年电影《一个美国人在巴黎》中的经典片段  歌曲名《I got rhythm》
♪ 在绿色牧场里 ♪
♪ In green pastures ♪
♪ 我得到了我的姑娘 ♪
♪ I've got my girl ♪
♪ 我还有什么好要求的呢 ♪
♪ Who could ask for anything more ♪
♪ 老人麻烦 ♪
♪ Old man trouble ♪
♪ 我不管它 ♪
♪ I don't mind him ♪
♪ 你不会发现 ♪
♪ You won't find him ♪
♪ 他在我家外面转悠 ♪
♪ Hanging 'round my door ♪
♪ 我有星光 ♪
♪ I've got starlight ♪
♪ 我有美梦 ♪
♪ I've got sweet dreams ♪
♪ 我有我的明星 ♪
♪ I've got my star ♪
♪ 我还有什么好要求的呢 ♪
♪ Who could ask for anything more? ♪
你那样看起来好危险啊
That looked dangerous.
不  你那个看起来才危险
No, that looks dangerous.
我们回来了
We're back.
试镜如何啦
Hey. How'd the audition go?
很好啊  我演主角
Great. I got the lead.
不是吧
You're kidding.
什么剧目啊
What's the play?
《安妮》
Annie.
1982年一部讲述红发女孩孤儿安妮的欢乐冒险的音乐剧
我要去学习我的台词了
I need to go learn my lines.
我刚听到时心里也有疑虑
Now, I was a little unsure at first,
但女演员桑迪·邓肯也曾反串演过《小飞侠》
but Sandy Duncan does play Peter Pan,
所以如果你仔细想想
so when you think about it...
康妮  你说这话纯帮倒忙
Connie, you're not helping.
好吧
Okay.
我想跟你聊聊这舞台剧的事
I want to talk to you about this play.
我也很兴奋
I'm excited about it, too.
你知道你要是扮演女孩角色
You know, if you play the part of a girl,
别人很有可能会取笑你吧
people might make fun of you.
伦迪先生想要冲击德州东部
Mr. Lundy's trying to push the boundaries
大家对戏剧的界限
of drama in East Texas.
其中一个方式就是女角男演
One way to do that is cross-gender casting.
让我修正一下我的措辞
Let me rephrase that:
如果你去扮女生  别人一定会取笑你
if you play the part of a girl, people will make fun of you.
在莎士比亚的年代  所有的女角都是男人演的
In Shakespeare's time, the men played all the female parts.
也没人取笑他们啊
No one made fun of it.
如果莎士比亚去上了公立学校
If Shakespeare went to public high school,
那情况就不会是这样了
it'd be a different story.
你知道桑迪·邓肯也演过男角色彼得潘吧
You know, Sandy Duncan plays the part of Peter Pan...
是啦  我听说了
Yeah, yeah, I heard.
儿子  爸爸是想保护你
I'm trying to protect you, son.
我谢谢你的好意
I appreciate that.
很好
Good.
你是个橄榄球教练
You're a football coach.
你的责任不就是
Isn't it your responsibility
把球员安排在最适合的位子上吗
to put in the best player for the job?
大概吧
I guess.
我想演戏
Well, I want to do this,
而伦迪先生说我是最棒的
and Mr. Lundy said I was the best.
好吧
Okay.
那你能起码穿裤子而不穿裙子吗
Can you at least wear pants instead of a dress?
我给你个十分肯定的可能吧
I'll give you a definite maybe.
{\an8\fn微软雅黑\fs18\b1\bord0\fad(500,0)\fsp1\shad3\3c&H000000&\fs22\pos(185.28,207.36)}三周后
好了  谁很期待啊
Okay, who's excited?
我不想看谢尔顿的白痴舞台剧  太丢人了
I don't want to see Sheldon's stupid play, it's humiliating.
这正是我想看的原因
That's why I want to see it.
我们要去支持你弟弟
We're going to support your brother.
我不想再听你们说任何一个字
Not another word about it.
我们能好歹坐到后排去吗
Can we at least sit in the back?
不许再说
Not a word.
我很期待啊
Well, I'm excited.
好了  大家  还有10分钟就开演了
Okay, everybody, ten minutes to curtain.
姑娘们  不许笑  生活很艰难
No smiling, girls, it's a hard knock life.
你怎么样啦  库珀先生
How you doing, Mr. Cooper?
跟内心的安妮起共鸣了吗
You in touch with your inner Annie?
有的吧
I believe so.
太好了  今天满座呢
Good. It's a packed house.
哇  什么鬼
Wha-- oh, what the heck?
凯蒂  凯蒂  你是孤儿
Katie? Katie. You're an orphan,
亲爱的  不是矿工
sweetheart, not a coal miner.
稍微收敛一点好吗
Let's tone that down, hmm?
老天爷啊
Oh, dear.
我做不来
I can't do this.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
舞台剧  我不行
The play, I can't do it.
外面太多人了
There are too many people out there.
你这是怯场
Oh, that is just stage fright.
这情况很正常
That's completely normal.
不  我这是恐慌症大发作
No, this is a full-blown panic attack.
好吧  你听我说
All right, listen to me.
你感到害怕
You're feeling scared.
我能理解  但你得知道
I get that, but what you have to understand
你不是独自一个人上台
is you're not going out on that stage alone.
各位  大家都集合过来
Everybody, gather around, hmm?
谢尔顿
Uh, Sheldon,
你去看过马戏团吗
have you ever been to the circus?
有
Yes.
很好
Okay, good.
我在那里也恐慌症发作了
I had a panic attack there, too.
我想说的是
My point is,
高空秋千表演永远都有安全网在下面
the trapeze artist always performs with a net
来接住他  保护他
to catch him, to protect him.
而你也被这里的大家保护着
And you are protected by everyone standing here.
在台上你不会有任何事
Nothing can happen to you out on that stage,
因为我们是个团队
because we're a team.
我们是你的安全网
We are your net.
我不知道了
I don't know.
谢尔顿  你过来
Sheldon, come here.
你
You...
就是个明星
are a star,
而外面的观众
and that audience
应该有机会看到你闪耀
deserves to see you shine.
伦迪先生的演说十分动人
Mr. Lundy gave a compelling speech.
的确该让观众有不虚此行的机会
The audience did deserve to see what they came for,
一个充满热情的男孩扮演着
an eager boy bravely taking on
小孤儿安妮这个角色
the role of Little Orphan Annie.
我看你是找揍
You're looking for a knuckle sandwich.
按这个来说  他们的确没有失望
And in that respect, they were not disappointed.
你们大家都安静
Pipe down, all of you.
快回去睡觉
Go back to sleep.
没事的  摩丽
It's all right, Molly.
安妮来了
Annie's here.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我很乐意说出89年在民风剽悍的德州东部
I'd tell you how an East Texas audience in 1989 responded
观众对于成年男人扮演安妮的反应
to a grown man playing Annie,
不过我想你们都猜得到
but I think you know.
我的台词是什么
What's my line?
♪ 明天太阳将升起 ♪
♪ The sun come out tomorrow ♪
歌曲名 - 《Tomorrow》
♪ 我跟你打包票  明天依旧 ♪
♪ Bet your bottom dollar that tomorrow ♪
♪ 会艳阳高照 ♪
♪ There'll be sun ♪
♪ 当我觉得日子灰暗 ♪
♪ When I'm stuck with a day that's gray ♪
♪ 与寂寞的时候 ♪
♪ And lonely ♪
♪ 我会抬起下巴  露出微笑 ♪
♪ I just stick out my chin and grin ♪
♪ 并说 ♪
♪ And say ♪
我好像看到了他的内裤
I think I see his underpants.
我就跟你说吧
I told you.
戏剧圈的人就爱露
Theatre folk just love to show off their business.
♪ 永远都会在新的一天到来 ♪
♪ Always a day away ♪
♪ 明天  明天 ♪
♪ Tomorrow, tomorrow ♪
♪ 我爱你  明天 ♪
♪ I love you, tomorrow ♪
♪ 你永远都会在 ♪
♪ You're always a day ♪
♪ 新的一天到来 ♪
♪ Away. ♪